The Biyei Hobo Rakurakujo in Marubilu has a
there is a sweet that puts in 1,000 pieces a month.
That is
Pudding made with a lot of Biei milk
The milk is made from pastured cows and is full of natural goodness.
The pudding is rich and juicy, but still soft and chewy!
Delicious!
The pudding has a strong milk flavor.
The slightly sweet and bittersweet caramel sauce is a perfect match!
Check out the latest pudding I want to try today!
The pudding at Monalita Coffee in Shimokitazawa is
I've been keeping an eye on the news on Instagram.
The pudding in a glass is the talk of the town on SNS!
It sells out every day!
Actually, it's served with espresso.
This pudding with espresso to melt the chocolate lid is very popular!
The pudding is filled with mascarpone.
So even though it is so firm, it is
but it is very smooth!
Topped with crunchy cookies and whipped cream!
and then cover it with bittersweet chocolate.
Tiramisu pudding is ready to sell out!
Mmmm...
The chocolate melts and mixes well with the pudding.
The pudding is smooth and the espresso soaked cookies are crunchy!
The Garden House CrafTS in Daikanzan has a great selection of pudding tarts.
Look at the pudding on the tart!
Crispy egg tart and soft pudding at the same time!
Egg tart made with 16 layers of croissant dough
and egg pudding made with plenty of eggs.
You can enjoy both of them at the same time!
The pudding is chunky and the egg tart is crispy, and the two textures are fun to eat!
The 101 Setagaya Road Pudding is
The 101 Setagaya Road pudding is a combination of Italian pudding and Brazilian pudding!
Italian pudding with mascarpone and other ingredients and
Brazilian sweets with two layers of pudding and cocoa flavored cake are combined
you can enjoy a pudding with a new texture.
The point is The point is.
We add Italian mascarpone and Hokkaido cream cheese!
The result is a smooth and creamy taste!
The cocoa article is
Baked with brown rice flour for added savory flavor
The bittersweet caramel sauce soaks into the dough
for an exquisite taste.
Thank you for watching!